Two return tickets to London, please.
两张到伦敦的往返票, 请.
What time will the next train leave?
下一班火车什么时候开?
At nineteen minutes past eight.
8点19分.
Which platform?
在哪个站台?
Platform Two. Over the bridge.
2号站台.过天桥.
What time will the next train leave?
下一班火车什么时候开?
At eight nineteen.
8点19分.
We've got plenty of time.
我们的时间还很宽裕.
It's only three minutes to eight.
现在才7点57分.
Let's go and have a drink.
让我们去喝点东西吧,
There's a bar next door to the station.
车站旁有一个酒吧.
We had better go back to the station now, Ken.
Ken,我们现在最好回到车站去.
Tickets, please.
请把车票拿出来.
We want to catch the eight nineteen to London.
我们要乘8点19分的车去伦敦.
You've just missed it!
你们刚好错过了那班车.
What! It's only eight fifteen.
什么!现在只有8点15分.
I'm sorry, sir.
对不起,先生,
That clock's ten minutes slow.
那个钟慢了10分钟.
When's the next train?
下一班车是什么时候?
In five hours' time!
5个小时以后!